Alina Gorelik

2577 Robins Way, Okemos, MI 48864 (517) 505-0309 ~ agorelik2@gmail.com

Skills

Strong programming and problem-solving skills proven under high-pressure environments. Working experience in HTML, JavaScript, ColdFusion, ASP, and SQL. After taking a break to raise three children, enrolled in full-stack web development bootcamp at Michigan State University to learn the latest technologies including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, GitBash.

Experience

Associated Bag Company, Milwaukee, WI

Independent Programming Contractor

June 2006 - August 2012

Senior Programmer-Analyst

March 2002 - June 2006

- Developed company's first e-commerce site using Microsoft Commerce Server
- Investigated and analized application alternatives to propose best design
- Translated corporate requirements into application specifications

Senior Programmer, Programmer

April 1997 - March 2002

- Designed and customized software for Sales, Purchasing, Inventory, and Accounting
- Maintained and expanded company's SQL, Access and Progress databases
- Completed report requests for Finance, Sales, Customer Service, and Purchasing

Education

Michigan State University Web Development Course June 2020 - November 2000

Full-Stack web development crash course that covered the latest technologies including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, GitBash.

Milwaukee Business Technical Institute, Milwaukee, WI May 1996 - March 1997

Business Computer Programming Certificate, March 1997

Minsk State Pedagogical University, Minsk, Belarus September 1985 - June 1990

Bachelor of Science in Physics, Minor in Computer Science

Strengths

Fast Learner, Self Motivated, Excellent Team Worker, Highly Organized, Detail Oriented